export const set6 = [
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 3 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["5", "6", "9", "2"],
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 7 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["5", "3", "7", "8"],
    answer: "7"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 8 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["15", "17", "16", "19"],
    answer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 3 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["6", "9", "3", "1"],
    answer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 6 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["11", "13", "12", "15"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 9 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["7", "9", "2", "5"],
    answer: "9"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 1 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["4", "2", "7", "9"],
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 5 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["3", "8", "5", "1"],
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 10 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["17", "20", "14", "18"],
    answer: "20"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 2 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["5", "2", "8", "3"],
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 4 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["3", "7", "8", "4"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 8 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["4", "9", "6", "8"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 7 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["13", "14", "11", "17"],
    answer: "14"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 4 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["7", "2", "5", "4"],
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 2 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["8", "3", "4", "1"],
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 10 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["10", "3", "6", "8"],
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 5 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["12", "10", "15", "13"],
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 6 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["9", "6", "4", "2"],
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">2 x 9 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["15", "17", "18", "14"],
    answer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <div class="row">1 x 1 = </div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1", "4", "7", "9"],
    answer: "1"
  }
];
